[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oliver Stone received his first Academy Award for Best Writing, Screenplay Based on Material from Another Medium for this 1978 movie.", "correct_answer": "Midnight Express", "incorrect_answers": ["JFK", "Platoon", "Wall Street"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1995 movie was awarded with the Oscar for Best Picture at the 68th Academy Awards ceremony in 1996?", "correct_answer": "Braveheart", "incorrect_answers": ["Sense and Sensibility", "Babe", "Apollo 13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Nero Wolfs legman and confidant?", "correct_answer": "Archie Goodwin", "incorrect_answers": ["Dr. Watson", "Coleman his butler", "Rex Stout"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The US Postal Service issued a series of stamps honoring these movies: Beau Geste, Gone With the Wind, The Wizard of Oz, and Stagecoach. What do these films have in common?", "correct_answer": "All were all released in the same year.", "incorrect_answers": ["They were all released by Warner Brothers.", "They all starred Clark Gable.", "They all had their premiers in California."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Urticaria is a relatively common form of allergic reaction, that causes red skin welts. Which is the other term which refers to this skin ailment?", "correct_answer": "Hives", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicken pox", "Shingles", "Eczema"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word deriving from Latin refers to the act of throwing someone or something out of a window.", "correct_answer": "defenestration", "incorrect_answers": ["sylvan", "peloton", "homunculus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would be in the workforce?", "correct_answer": "484", "incorrect_answers": ["762", "895", "225"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Leonardo da Vinci is well known as the artist who painted the Mona Lisa, but he was also an inventor.  Which modern-day machine is based on one of his concepts?", "correct_answer": "helicopter", "incorrect_answers": ["radio", "chain saw", "blender"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What video game sparked a huge craze and inspired a TV series which aired on ABC from 1982 to 1984?", "correct_answer": "Pac-man", "incorrect_answers": ["Pong", "Defender", "Space Invaders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Potatoes are used in millions of cooking recipes around the globe. Which of these dishes contains potatoes?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Chochoca", "Milcaos", "Champ"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the first routine that Chazz Michael Michaels and Jimmy MacElroy do together in the movie Blades of Glory?", "correct_answer": "Fire and Ice", "incorrect_answers": ["Dont Want to Miss a Thing", "Together", "Fire and Water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Robert Altman first went to Hollywood, he tried different activities, including working as the publicity director in the business of tattooing dogs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]